My child arrived just the other day.
He came to the world in the usual way.
But there were planes to catch and bills to pay.
He learned to walk while I was away.
And he was talking before I knew it.
And as he grew, he'd say,
I'm going to be like you, Dad.
You know I'm going to be like you.
My child arrived just the other day.
He came to the world in the usual way.
But there were planes to catch and bills to pay.
He learned to walk while I was away.
And he was talking before I knew it.
And as he grew, he'd say,
I'm going to be like you, Dad.
You know I'm going to be like you.
Chorus.
And the cats in the cradle and the silver spoon.
Little boy blue and the man in the moon.
When you coming home, Dad?
I don't know when.
But we'll get together then.
You know we'll have a good time then.
And the cats in the cradle and the silver spoon.
Little boy blue and the man in the moon.
When you coming home, Dad?
I don't know when.
But we'll get together then.
You know we'll have a good time then.
Part two.
My son turned ten just the other day.
He said, "Thanks for the ball, dad,
come on, let’s play.
You know I’m going to be like him.
I called him up just the other day.
I said, “I’d like to see you if you don’t mind." He said, "
I’d love to, Dad, if I can find the time.
You see, my new job’s a worry and the kids have the flu,
But it’s sure nice talking to you,
dad.
It’s sure been nice talking to you." And as I hung up the phone,
it occurred to me, He’d grown up just like me.
My boy was just like me.